Guide to the Pirie MacDonald Portrait Photographs [1885]-1942 (bulk 1900-1942) PR 39
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Portrait Photographs
  - Nicholson, Meredith (1866-1947), author, diplomat, lecturer, 1922 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 283)
  - Nicoll, DeLancey (1854-1931), lawyer, 1908 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 284)
  - Nixon, Lewis (1861-1940), shipbuilder, 1903 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 285)
  - O'Brien, Morgan Joseph (1852-1937), jurist, 1907 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 286)
  - O'Casey, Sean (1881-1964), Irish playwright, 1934 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 287)
  - Ochs, Adolph S. (1858-1935), publisher, 1911 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 288)
  - Ochtman, Leonard (1854-1934), painter, 1913 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 289)
  - Oenslager, Donald Mitchell (1902-1975), scenic designer, 1937 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 290)
  - Olcott, Jacob Van Vechten (1856-1940), politician, 1905 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 291)
  - Opper, Frederick Burr (1857-1937), illustrator, 1903 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 292)
  - Overton, Grant (1887-1930), author, 1928 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 293)
  - Page, Curtis Hidden (1870-1946), writer, editor, educator, 1914 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 294)
  - Paine, Albert Bigelow (1861-1937), author, editor, 1932 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 295)
  - Parker, Alton Brooks (1853-1926), jurist, 1906 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 296)
  - Parker, Gilbert (1862-1932), English novelist, 1913 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 297)
  - Parker, Herschel Clifford (b. 1867), physicist, 1911 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 298)
  - Parkhurst, Charles Henry (1842-1933), clergyman, 1906 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 299)
  - Pinchot, Gifford (1865-1946), politician, conservationist, 1909 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 300)
  - Pine, John (1857-1922), lawyer, 1908 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 301)
  - Pirie, John Taylor (1871-1940), merchant, 1905 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 302)
  - Platt, Charles Adams (1861-1933), architect, painter, 1921 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 303)
  - Platt, Thomas Collier (1833-1910), politician, 1903 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 304)
  - Poore, Henry Rankin (1859-1940), painter, author, 1914 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 305)
  - Pope, John Russell (1874-1937), architect, 1911 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 306)
  - Posner, Michael (b. 1890), violinist, 1919 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 307)
  - Powell, John (1882-1963), composer, pianist [three-quarter pose, facing left], 1931 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 308)
  - Putnam, Herbert (1861-1955), librarian, 1936 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 309)
  - Raskob, John J. (1879-1950), businessman, 1922 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 310)
  - Rentschler, Gordon S. (1885-1948), banker, industrialist, 1940 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 311)
  - Rhind, John Massey (1858-1936), sculptor, 1911 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 312)
  - Riis, Jacob August (1849-1914), author, 1906 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 313)
  - Roberts, Kenneth (1885-1957), author, 1936 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 314)
  - Robinson, Douglas (1855-1918), businessman, 1908 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 315)
  - Robinson, Edwin Arlington (1869-1935), poet, 1929 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 316)
  - Robinson, Lennox (1886-1958), Irish playwright, author, 1933 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 317)
  - Roche, James Jeffrey (1847-1908), editor, 1903 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 318)
  - Rogers, Bruce (1870-1957), book designer, 1932 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 319)
  - Roosevelt, Nicholas (1893-1965), author, diplomat [in military uniform], 1917 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 320)
  - Roosevelt, Nicholas (1893-1965), author, diplomat [in business suit], 1938 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 321)
  - Ross, Hugh (b. 1898), conductor, 1936 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 322)
  - Roth, Ernest David (1879-1964), painter, printmaker, 1934 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 323)
  - Sabin, Charles Hamilton (1868-1933), banker, 1909 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 324)
  - Sachse, Julius Frederich (1842-1919), historian, 1908 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 325)
  - Sage, Russell (1816-1906), financier, 1903 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 326)
  - Sarnoff, David (1891-1971), businessman, 1923 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 327)
  - Sassoon, Siegfried (1886-1967), English poet, 1920 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 328)
  - Schelling, Ernest Henry (1876-1939), pianist, composer, conductor [profile pose], 1931 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 329)
  - Schiff, Mortimer L. (1877-1931), banker, 1911 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 330)
  - Schurz, Carl Lincoln (1871-1924), lawyer, publicist, 1908 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 331)
  - Schwab, Charles M. (1862-1939), industrialist, 1917 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 332)
  - Shackleton, Ernest (1874-1922), English explorer, 1913 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 333)
  - Shattuck, Frank G. (1860-1937), businessman, 1917 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 334)
  - Shaw, Albert (1857-1947), author, editor, 1902 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 335)
  - Sheldon, Edward Brewster (1886-1946), playwright, 1914 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 336)
  - Shelley, Harry Rowe (1858-1947), organist, composer, 1936 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 337)
  - Sherwood, Robert Emmet (1896-1955), playwright, 1940 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 338)
  - Shipman, Herbert (1869-1930) clergyman, 1916 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 339)
  - Sitwell, Francis Osbert (1892-1969), English poet, playwright, novelist, 1926 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 340)
  - Skinner, Otis (1858-1942), actor, 1917 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 341)
  - Sloan, Alfred Pritchard, Jr. (1873-1966), industrialist, 1922 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 342)
  - Sloan, William Milligan (1850-1928), educator, 1915 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 343)
  - Smith, David Stanley (1877-1949), composer, 1933 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 344)
  - Smith, Jonas Waldo (1861-1933), civil engineer, 1924 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 345)
  - Spaeth, Sigmund (1885-1965), writer, musician, lecturer, 1935 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 346)
  - Speicher, Eugene Edward (1883-1962), artist, 1936 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 347)
  - Spencer, Lorillard (1883-1939), industrialist, 1921 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 348)
  - Sproule, William (1858-1935), railway executive, 1916 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 349)
  - Stanchfield, John Barry (1855-1921), lawyer, 1913 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 350)
  - Stedman, Edmund Clarence (1833-1908), poet, critic, 1903 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 351)
  - Stefansson, Vilahjalmur (1879-1962), explorer, writer, 1924 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 352)
  - Steffens, (Joseph) Lincoln (1866-1936), writer, lecturer, 1912 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 353)
  - Stephens, James (1882-1950) Irish poet, author, 1925 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 354)
  - Stern, Louis (1847-1922), merchant, 1904 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 355)
  - Stettinius, Edward R. Sr., (1865-1925), banker, 1917 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 356)
  - Stettinius, Edward R., Jr. (1900-1949), government official, 1933 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 357)
  - Stock, Frederick A. (1872-1942), conductor, 1936 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 358)
  - Stoessel, Albert F. (1894-1943), composer, conductor, 1932 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 359)
  - Stout, Rex Todhunter (1886-1975), author, 1926 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 360)
  - Straus, Jesse Isidor (1872-1936), merchant, diplomat, 1931 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 361)
  - Straus, Oscar Solomon (1850-1926), merchant, diplomat, 1902 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 362)
  - Straus, Percy Seldon (1876-1944), merchant, 1940 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 363)
  - Street, Julian (1879-1947), author, 1911 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 364)
  - Strong, Austin (1881-1952), author, dramatist, 1936 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 365)
  - Strong, Benjamin (1872-1928), banker, 1914 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 366)
  - Stryker, Melancthon Woolsey (1851-1929), college president, 1912 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 367)
  - Sullivan, Mark (1874-1952), author, journalist, 1916 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 368)
  - Sulzberger, Cyrus L. (1858-1932), merchant, 1906 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 369)
  - Swinnerton, Frank Arthur (1884-1982), English author, critic, 1924 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 370)
  - Taft, Lorado (1860-1936), sculptor, 1923 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 371)
  - Tarkington, Booth (1869-1946), novelist, playwright, 1919 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 372)
  - Taylor, Myron Charles (1874-1959), lawyer, banker, diplomat, 1936 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 373)
  - Terhune, Albert Payson (1872-1942), author, dog fancier, 1922 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 374)
  - Thayer, Harry Bates (1858-1936), businessman, 1915 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 375)
  - Thomas, Augustus (1857-1934), playwright, 1918 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 376)
  - Thomas, Lowell (1892-1981), author, lecturer, commentator, 1933 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 377)
  - Thomas, Norman M. (1884-1968), author, editor, politician, 1932 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 378)
  - Tinker, Chauncey Brewster (1876-1963), educator, author, 1940 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 379)
  - Torrence, (Frederick) Ridgely (1875-1950), author, poet, dramatist, 1933 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 380)
  - Torrey, George Burroughs (1863-1942), painter, 1915 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 381)
  - Trask, Spencer (1844-1909), banker, 1900 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 382)
  - Tryon, Dwight William (1849-1925), painter, 1906 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 383)
  - Tutchings, Everett, organist, choirmaster, 1938 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 384)
  - Underwood, Frederick Douglass (1849-1942), businessman, 1905 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 385)
  - Untermeyer, Louis (1885-1977), author, editor poet, 1920 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 386)
  - Vail, Theodore Newton (1845-1920), businessman, 1908 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 387)
  - van Dyke, Henry (1852-1933), author, clergyman, diplomat, 1916 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 388)
  - Van Dyke, John Charles (1856-1932), author, educator, 1923 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 389)
  - van Loon, Hendrick Willem (1882-1944), author, 1937 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 390)
  - Volk, Douglas (1856-1935), painter, 1931 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 391)
  - Wadsworth, James Wolcott (1877-1952), politician, 1912 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 392)
  - Walpole, Hugh (1884-1941), English novelist, 1930 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 393)
  - Walsh, Thomas Joseph (1882-1952), banker, 1931 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 394)
  - Waltman, Harry Franklin (1871-1951), painter, 1933 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 395)
  - Wanamaker, John (1838-1922), merchant, 1909 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 396)
  - Wanger, Walter (1894-1968), motion picture producer, 1925 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 397)
  - Warburg, Felix (1871-1937), banker, 1913 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 398)
  - Watrous, Harry Wilson (1857-1940), painter, 1936 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 399)
  - Whiting, Arthur (1861-1936), musician, composer, 1931 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 400)
  - Whitlock, Brand (1869-1934), author, diplomat, 1924 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 401)
  - Whitman, Charles Seymour (1868-1947), politician [three-quarter pose, pearl stickpin], 1913 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 402)
  - Whitman, Charles Seymour (1868-1947), politician [three-quarter pose, striped tie], 1933 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 403)
  - Whitney, Cornelius Vanderbilt (b. 1899), businessman, 1939 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 404)
  - Wiggin, Albert Henry (1868-1951), banker, 1909 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 405)
  - Wilder, Thornton (1897-1975), author, playwright, 1940 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 406)
  - Wiley, Harvey Washington (1844-1930), chemist, author, 1916 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 407)
  - Willard, Daniel (1861-1942), businessman, 1921 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 408)
  - Willys, John North (1873-1935), manufacturer, diplomat, 1910 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 409)
  - Wilson, Woodrow (1856-1924), educator, politician [pose in academic robe], 1902 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 410)
  - Wilson, Woodrow (1856-1924), educator, politician [pose in business suit], 1902 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 411)
  - Winter, Ezra Augustus (1886-1949), painter, 1938 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 412)
  - Wise, Stephen Samuel (1874-1949), clergyman, 1913 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 413)
  - Wister, Owen (1860-1938), author, 1915 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 414)
  - Wodehouse, Pelham Grenville (1881-1975), English author, 1922 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 415)
  - Wood, Eric Fisher (1889-1962), author, architect, military officer, 1941 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 416)
  - Woods, Arthur (1870-1942), government official, 1917 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 417)
  - Youtz, Philip Newell (1895-1972), architect, museum director, 1934 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 418)
  - Ziegler, William, Jr. (1891-1957), industrialist, 1934 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 419)
- Oversized Portraits
  From Series I: Portrait Photographs
  - Adler, Felix (1851-1933) lecturer and educator, 1926 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 420)
  - Alden, Henry Mills (1836-1919), editor, 1915 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 421)
  - Amundsen, Roald (1872-1928), explorer, 1918 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 422)
  - Arcularius, Charles DuBois, designer of metalwork, 1936 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 423)
  - Beach, Rex (1877-1949), author, 1922 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 424)
  - Bishop, William Avery (1894-1956), Canadian airman, 1918 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 425)
  - Brooks, A. L., 1923 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 426)
  - Burt, Struthers (1882-1954), author, rancher, 1925 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 427)
  - Burton, Spence (b. 1881), clergyman, 1929 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 428)
  - Cardozo, Benjamin Nathan (1870-1938), jurist [three-quarter pose, with glasses], 1927 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 429)
  - Carson, Donald, 1925 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 430)
  - Chadwick, George Whitefield (1854-1931), organist, composer, conductor, 1922 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 431)
  - Chesterton, Gilbert Keith (1864-1936), author, 1921 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 432)
  - Clark, William Andrews (1839-1925), banker, mine owner, politician, 1917 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 433)
  - Colum, Padraic, (1881-1972), poet, dramatist, 1923 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 434)
  - Cortissoz, Royal (1869-1948), editor, critic, author, lecturer, 1932 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 435)
  - Coward, Noel (1899-1973), English playwright, composer, actor, 1928 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 436)
  - Cox, Jennings S., Jr. (1867-1913), mining engineer and metallurgist, 1911 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 437)
  - Crane, Frank (1861-1928), journalist, author, 1921 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 438)
  - Crawford, Jack (1847-1917), frontiersman, poet, 1915 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 439)
  - Cromwell, William Nelson (1854-1948), lawyer, 1939 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 440)
  - Crosby, Percy (1891-1964), author, artist, illustrator, 1935 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 441)
  - Cummins, John F. (1852-1933), clergyman, 1916 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 442)
  - Damrosch, Walter Johannes (1862-1950), conductor, composer [profile pose, gray jacket], 1936 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 443)
  - Fisher, Harrison (1877-1934), artist [profile pose], 1922 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 444)
  - Flagg, James Montgomery (1877-1960), artist, author, 1928 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 445)
  - Gallen, Patrick Henry (1855-1934), clergyman, 1923 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 446)
  - Gottesman, Mendel (1859-1942), banker, 1939 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 447)
  - Grew, Joseph Clark (1880-1965), diplomat, 1926 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 448)
  - Hoving, Walter (1897-1989), businessman, 1939 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 449)
  - Hunt, Godfrey (1878-1934), clergyman, 1920 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 450)
  - Huxley, Aldous Leonard (1894-1963), English novelist, essayist, 1926 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 451)
  - Lang, William Cosmo Gordon (1864-1945), English clergyman [head and shoulders, dark jacket], 1922 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 452)
  - Lawrence, William (1850-1941), clergyman [profile pose], 1916 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 453)
  - Lie, Jonas (1880-1940), painter, 1935 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 454)
  - Lodge, Oliver (1951-1940), English scientist [full frontal pose], 1920 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 455)
  - Lunt, Alfred (1892-1977), actor, director, 1923 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 456)
  - McIntyre, Oscar Odd (1884-1938), writer, 1922 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 457)
  - MacMonnies, Frederick (1863-1937), sculptor, 1917 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 458)
  - Masefield, John (1878-1967), English poet, 1933 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 459)
  - Meigs, Ramsey, actor, 1925 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 460)
  - Nelson, Charles N., yachtsman, 1917 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 461)
  - Nelson, William Rockhill (1841-1915), publisher, 1910 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 462)
  - Nichols, Beverley (1889-1983), English author, 1927 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 463)
  - Nichols, Jesse Brooks, military officer, 1927 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 464)
  - O'Malley, Power (1878-1946), painter, 1933 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 465)
  - Parker, Horatio William (1863-1919), composer, 1915 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 466)
  - Pennell, Joseph (1860-1926), printmaker, 1922 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 467)
  - Perot, Edward S., Jr., (1919-1963), aviator, 1939 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 468)
  - Philbin, Ewing R. (1889-1957), lawyer, 1917 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 469)
  - Powell, John (1882-1963), composer, pianist [three-quarter pose, facing right], 1931 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 470)
  - Preistley, John Boynton (1894-1984),, English novelist, dramatist, 1931 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 471)
  - Riddle, John Wallace (1864-1941), diplomat, 1930 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 472)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore (1858-1937), politician, 1915 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 473)
  - Root, Elihu (1845-1937), statesman, jurist, diplomat, 1917 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 474)
  - Russell, George (1867-1935) ["AE"], Irish poet, painter, 1928 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 475)
  - Sachs, Julius (1849-1934), educator, 1914 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 476)
  - Sarg, Tony (1882-1942), designer, lecturer, puppeteer, 1923 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 477)
  - Schelling, Ernest Henry (1876-1939), pianist, composer, conductor [three-quarter pose], 1931 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 478)
  - Seton, Ernest Thompson (1860), naturalist, painter, author, 1914 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 479)
  - Simonson, Lee (1888), scenic designer, author, 1930 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 480)
  - Stedman, Giles (1897), naval officer, 1933 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 481)
  - Sterner, Albert E. (1863), painter, printmaker, 1923 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 482)
  - Streeter, Burnett Hillman (1874) English clergyman, 1928 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 483)
  - Taylor, Deems (1885-1966), composer, writer, commentator, 1931 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 484)
  - Train, Arthur, lawyer, author, 1922 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 485)
  - Vaughn, Bernard (1847-1922), English clergyman, 1912 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 486)
  - Von Galen, Clemens August, German clergyman, 1925 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 487)
  - Wallace, Edgar (1875-1932), English novelist, 1929 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 488)
  - Ward, William L. (1856-1933), manufacturer, 1923 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 489)
  - Watterson, Henry (1840-1921), editor, 1919 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 490)
  - Weir, J. Alden (1832-1919), painter, 1913 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 491)
  - Williamson, Henry F., English author, journalist, 1930 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 492)
  - Woollcott, Alexander (1887-1943), journalist, critic, 1930 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 493)
  - Yeats, William Butler (1865-1939), Irish poet, dramatist, 1932 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 494)
- Series II. Documentary Material
  Arranged in two subseries: Ephemera; Card Files
  - Ephemera-Studio window signs: Signs used after April 1942 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 495)
  - Ephemera-Studio window signs: Noel Coward and Alfred Lunt sign, 1933 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 496)
  - Ephemera-Studio window signs: "Studio open," "on this corner…" and vacation signs, undated (Offsite-box 22, Folder 497)
  - Stationery: Copyright and invoice forms, undated (Offsite-box 22, Folder 498)
  - Stationery: Labels, undated (Offsite-box 22, Folder 499)
  - Stationery: Letterhead and envelopes, undated (Offsite-box 22, Folder 500)
  - Stationery: Stickers and seals, undated (Offsite-box 22, Folder 501)
  - Original artwork: Calligraphy for Albany studio, [1895] (Offsite-box 22, Folder 502)
  - Original artwork: Designs by Charles Selkirk, [1900] (Offsite-box 22, Folder 503)
  - Original artwork: "A Note of Distinction", undated (Offsite-box 22, Folder 504)
  - Portrait card signed by Pirie MacDonald, 1938 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 505)
  - Miscellaneous printed ephemera, undated (Offsite-box 22, Folder 506)
  - Photographs: Six miniature portraits of Albanians, [1895] (Offsite-box 22, Folder 507)
  - Photographs: Signature, undated (Offsite-box 22, Folder 508)
  - Copy prints "for half-tone reproduction" of Arnold Bennett (two prints), Van Wyck Brooks, Nicholas Butler, Charles Hughes, Thomas Masaryk (two prints), J. B. Priestley, Theodore Roosevelt, Lee Simonson, Sigmund Spaeth, Alexander Woollcott (two prints), undated (Offsite-box 22, Folder 509)
  - Studio patron cards: A-I, 1900-1940 (Offsite-box 23)
  - Studio patron cards: J-S, 1900-1940 (Offsite-box 24)
  - Studio patron cards: T-Z, 1900-1940 (Offsite-box 25)
  - Miscellaneous cards in two series, A-Z, A-Z, undated (Offsite-box 25)
  - Negative Index Cards: 1901-1929 set, A-Z (Offsite-box 26)
  - Negative Index Cards: 1909-1914 set, A-Z (Offsite-box 26)
  - Negative Index Cards: 1914-1942 set, A-F (Offsite-box 26)
  - Negative Index Cards: 1914-1942 set, G-Z (Offsite-box 27)